Plant-based meats are coming soon to a dinner table near you, but do they deserve a spot on your plate?
植物肉很快就会出现在你身边的餐桌上，但它们配得上在你的盘子里占有一席之地吗？
If you tried a vegetable burger years ago and dismissed it as rubbery and flavorless, it’s a good time to give meatless meat another chance.
如果你多年前尝过蔬菜汉堡，觉得它像橡胶一样难嚼、淡而无味，便对它不屑一顾，那么现在正是再给素肉一次机会的好时机。
Newer varieties imitate the look, flavor, and texture of meat.
较新的品种模仿肉的外观、风味和口感。
Analysts don’t expect the meat-free movement to slow anytime soon; a 2021 report predicts the market will skyrocket to $74 billion by 2030—a 957 percent surge.
分析人士预计，无肉运动短期内不会放缓；2021年的一份报告预测，到2030年，这一市场的规模将飙升至740亿美元，增幅达957%。
Plant-based meats are no longer just for vegetarians.
植物肉不再只面向素食者。
Companies such as Impossible Foods and Beyond Meat—the current superstars of the alternative protein sector—are pursuing consumers who enjoy meat but want to reduce their meat consumption for animal rights, health, or environmental reasons.
Impossible Foods和Beyond Meat是当前替代蛋白领域的超级明星，这类公司正在争取这样一批消费者：喜欢吃肉，但出于动物权益、健康或环保方面的原因，想减少肉类消费。
So far, it’s a winning strategy: More than nine out of ten consumers who buy Beyond Burger and Impossible Foods products also eat meat.
到目前为止，这一策略很成功：购买Beyond Burger和Impossible Foods产品的消费者中，超过九成也吃肉。
Many vegetarians don’t actually care for food that resembles meat.
许多素食者其实并不喜欢类似肉的食物。
When reporter Joan Solsman, a longtime vegetarian, tried a dish from Impossible Foods, she felt so sick that she couldn’t finish it.
记者琼·索尔斯曼多年来一直是素食者，她尝了一道Impossible Foods的菜，结果恶心得没能吃完。
“Maybe the best sign that Impossible Foods has cracked the code to realistic fake meat is that I couldn’t stand to take another bite,” she wrote.
“Impossible Foods已经找到了做出逼真假肉的诀窍，最能说明这一点的，或许就是我连再吃一口都受不了，”她写道。
Meatless meats are generally a healthier choice than beef because they are cholesterol-free, plus they’re a good source of vitamins, minerals, protein, and fiber.
素肉通常是比牛肉更健康的选择，因为它们不含胆固醇，而且还是维生素、矿物质、蛋白质和膳食纤维的良好来源。
If meatless meat can help you stick to a plant-based diet, that in itself can lead to better health.
如果素肉能帮你坚持以植物为主的饮食，这本身就能让你更健康。
Not only has red meat been linked to cancer, but studies show that people who ditch meat have lower blood pressure, lower average blood sugar, and lower cholesterol levels.
不仅红肉已被发现与癌症有关，而且研究表明，放弃吃肉的人血压更低，平均血糖更低，胆固醇水平也更低。
However, just because it’s plant-based doesn’t mean it’s health food.
然而，不能因为它以植物为原料，就认为它是健康食品。
Most imitation meats are highly processed and contain high amounts of sodium compared to traditional beef.
大多数仿制肉都经过高度加工，而且与传统牛肉相比，含钠量很高。
These new generations of alternate meat get all the attention, but don’t forget about whole grains and vegetables.
这些新一代替代肉抢尽了风头，但别忘了全谷物和蔬菜。
Beans are an especially excellent protein substitute.
豆类是一种尤为出色的蛋白质替代品。
They’re nutritious, inexpensive, and far more sustainable than any of the processed meatless substitutes on the market today.
它们营养丰富，价格低廉，而且比当今市场上任何一种经过加工的无肉替代品都要可持续得多。